Guide to the Dorothy Schefer Faux fashion collection, 1931-2017.
Faux, Dorothy Schefer fashion collection
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Dorothy Schefer Faux fashion collection, 1931-2017.
8572
Faux, Dorothy Schefer.
23.4 cubic feet.
Publications, printed materials, photographs, and video tapes and reel to reel recordings.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Collection offers a depth of material related to fashion design in the later half of the 20th century with most dating from the 1990 to 2016.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Dorothy Schefer Faux, Cornell University Class of 1969, is a former senior editor of Vogue, an author, and entrepreneur.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Collection offers a depth of material related to fashion design in the later half of the 20th century with most dating from the 1990 to 2016. Material in the collection consists of lookbooks, Visionaires, designer interviews, VHS tapes and other media, and other publications and books related to fashion.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Faux, Dorothy Schefer.; Cornell University -- Students.; Cornell University -- Alumni and alumnae.; Cornell University. Class of 1969.
Subjects:
Fashion designers.; Fashion design.; Fashion editors -- United States.; Costume design.; Artists' books.; Clothing and dress.; Fashion
Form and Genre Terms:
Ephemera.; Video cassettes.; Video tapes; Records.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
SERIES LIST
Series I. Look books
Series II. Trend reports
a. Vogue trend reports
b. Other trend reports
Series III. Event publications
a. Bonnie Cashin: designer's season descriptions and/or illustrations
b. Exhibit Catalogs
c. Various event publications
Series IV. Fashion Publications
a. Books
b. Visionaire
c. Fashion and Various Other Periodicals
Series V. Promotional materials and fashion show invitations
a. Promotional materials
b. Fashion show invitations
Series VI. Designer interviews
a. Binder A
b. Binder B
Series VII. Media
a. Videos
b. Tape recordings
c. Records
CONTAINER LIST
- Look books, 1983, 1991-2007
  Arranged in alphabetical order by designer and then by date.
  - "The Designers" Saks Fifth Avenue, Spring 2002; LB 68 (Box 17)
  - Anya Hinmarch "Be A Bag", Fall-Winter; LB 96; Anya Hinmarch (Box 17)
  - BCBG MaxAzria Ready-To-Wear, Fall 2004; LB 135 (Box 17)
  - Bergdorf Goodman Designers, Fall 1992; LB 4 (Box 17)
  - Bergdorf Goodman, Summer-Spring 2001; LB 55; Chanel (Box 17)
  - Bergdorf Goodman, Fall 2017 (Box 34)
    Accessories
  - Best & Co., Fall 2004; LB 109; Hilfiger, Susie (Box 18)
  - Betsey Johnson (Spring), Undated; LB 185 (Box 18)
  - Burberry London, Undated; LB 138 (Box 18)
  - Calvin Klein- Fragrance, Color, Skincare, 2000; LB 40; Calvin Klein (Box 17)
  - Calvin Klein Collection, Spring 2000; LB 41; Calvin Klein (Box 17)
  - Calvin Klein Accessories Spring/Summer 2001, Spring-Summer 2001; LB 52; Calvin Klein (Box 17)
  - Calvin Klein Collection, Summer-Spring 2001; LB 54; Calvin Klein (Box 17)
  - Calvin Klein Collection, Fall 2001; LB 66; Calvin Klein (Box 17)
  - Calvin Klein Home 2003, Fall-Winter 2003; LB 85; Calvin Klein (Box 17)
  - Calvin Klein Collection, Spring 2004; LB 132 (Box 17)
    Invitation enclosed
  - Calvin Klein Collection, Winter 2004; LB 100 (Box 17)
  - Calvin Klein Jeans, Undated; LB 108 (Box 17)
  - Carolina Herrera, Spring 2000; LB 180 (Box 18)
  - Chanel Collection, Fall-Winter 1992-1993; LB 7; Chanel (Box 19)
  - Chanel Collection, Fall-Winter 1992-1993; LB 9; Lagerfeld, Karl (Box 17)
  - Chanel Boutique Collection, Summer-Spring 1993; LB 13; Chanel (Box 19)
  - Chanel Joaillerie, Summer-Spring 1993; LB 14; Lagerfeld, Karl (Box 17)
  - Chanel Boutique Collection, Fall-Winter 1993-1994; LB 16; Lagerfeld, Karl (Box 19)
  - Chanel Accessories, Winter-Fall 1996; LB 19; Lagerfeld, Karl (Box 17)
    Invitation and Catalog of Postcards
  - Chanel Boutique Collection Croisiere, 1996-1997; LB 161 (Box 24)
  - Chanel Joaillerie (Jewelry), 1997; LB 22; Lagerfeld, Karl (Box 17)
  - Chanel Ready To Wear, Winter-Fall 1997-1998; LB 27; Chanel (Box 19)
    Includes letter
  - Chanel Ready To Wear, Summer-Spring 1998; LB 29; Chanel (Box 19)
  - Chanel Cruise Collection, Summer-Spring 1998; LB 21; Chanel (Box 19)
  - Chanel Boutique Collection, Fall-Winter 1998-1999; LB 34; Chanel (Box 17)
  - Chanel, Summer-Spring 1999; LB 36 (Box 17)
    3 copies
  - Chanel, 2000; LB 152 (Box 24)
  - Chanel Boutique Ready-To=Wear & Accessories, Summer-Spring 2000; LB 178 (Box 18)
    Includes price list
  - Chanel Ski Wear Ready-To-Wear & Accessories, Fall-Winter 2000; LB 47; Lagerfeld, Karl (Box 17)
  - Chanel Boutique Ready-To-Wear & accessories, Fall-Winter 2000-2001; LB 181 (Box 18)
    Includes bookmark
  - Chanel Boutique, Fall-Winter 2000-2001; LB 64; Chanel (Box 17)
    Invitation
  - Chanel Collection, Summer-Spring 2001; LB 57; Chanel (Box 17)
  - Chanel Cruise Collection, Winter 2001; LB 56; Chanel (Box 17)
  - Chanel SPORT, Spring-Summer 2002; LB 69; Chanel (Box 17)
  - Chanel Cocogirls Ready To Wear, Fall-Winter 2002-2003; LB 74; Chanel (Box 17)
  - Chanel SPORT, Fall-Winter 2002-2003; LB 78; Chanel (Box 17)
  - Chanel, Spring-Summer 2003; LB 93 (Box 17)
    Comes with CD titled "Fashion Exhibition" (CD is inside catalog)
  - Chanel Accessories Collection, Fall-Winter 2003-2004; LB 94 (Box 17)
  - Chanel, Fall-Winter 2003-2004; LB 91; Lagerfeld, Karl (Box 17)
    Catalog of Postcards
  - Chanel, Spring-Summer 2004; LB 119; Lagerfeld, Karl (Box 17)
  - Chanel Accessories Collection, Spring-Summer 2004; LB 88; Lagerfeld, Karl (Box 17)
  - Chanel, 2004; LB 97; Lagerfeld, Karl (Box 18)
  - Chanel, 2004; LB 122 (Box 18)
  - Chanel Pre-Fa/Wi, Fall-Winter 2004-2005; LB 102 (Box 18)
  - Chanel, Undated (Box 25)
  - D. Porthault, 2001; LB 45 (Box 17)
    Business card attached: Carol Procope-Jackson
  - D. Porthault, 2000 (Box 17)
  - D. Porthault, 2001; LB 48 (Box 17)
  - Diane Von Furstenberg "Le Grand Tour", Spring 2005; LB 104 (Box 18)
  - Dior Leather Goods Collection, 1997; LB 173; Dior, Christian (Box 18)
    Catalog and price list
  - Dior Christian Dior Accessories, Fall-Winter 1999-2000; LB 38; Christian Dior (Box 17)
  - Dolce & Gabbana Collezione Donna White Label, Fall-Winter 2000-2001; LB 170 (Box 18)
  - Dolce & Gabbana White Label Collection, Fall-Winter 2000-2001; LB 61; Dolce & Gabbana (Box 17)
  - Dolce & Gabbana White Label Collection, Fall-Winter 2000-2001; LB 61; Dolce & Gabbana (Box 17)
  - Dolce & Gabbana White Label Collection, Spring-Summer 2001; LB 60; Dolce & Gabbana (Box 17)
  - Dolce & Gabbana White Label Collection, Spring-Summer 2001; LB 60; Dolce & Gabbana (Box 17)
  - Dolce & Gabbana White Label Collection, Fall-Winter 2001-2002; LB 62; Dolce & Gabbana (Box 17)
  - Dolce & Gabbana White Label Collection, Fall-Winter 2001-2002; LB 62; Dolce & Gabbana (Box 17)
  - Dolce & Gabbana White Label, Spring-Summer 2002; LB 70; Dolce & Gabbana (Box 17)
  - DKNY NYC, 1994; Donna Karan Company (Box 26)
  - Donna Karan New York (DKNY), 1996; LB 20 (Box 24)
  - Donna Karan New York, 1996; Donna Karan Company (Box 26)
  - DKNY: Soul of the City, Undated; DKNY (Box 25)
  - DKNY, Undated; Donna Karan Company (Box 26)
  - Dosa, Spring-Summer 2001 (Box 25)
  - Douglas Hannant, Fall-Winter 2000; LB 175 (Box 18)
    Individual pages of photographs with letter (addressed to "Phyllis Schefer") in notebook folder
  - Emilio Pucci, Spring-Summer 2004; LB 89 (Box 17)
  - Eres Lingerie, Spring-Summer 2004; LB 106 (Box 17)
  - Fendi, Fall-Winter 1999-2000; LB 184 (Box 18)
  - Fendi, Spring-Summer 2000; LB 188 (Box 18)
    Matchbook-style catalog with mailing envelope
  - Fendi, Spring-Summer 2003; LB 81 (Box 17)
  - Fendi Bags, Spring-Summer 2003; LB 80; Fendi (Box 17)
  - Fendi Bags, Spring-Summer 2003; LB 82; Fendi (Box 17)
  - Fendi Stores, 2003; LB 84; Fendi (Box 17)
  - Fendi, Undated; LB 169 (Box 18)
    Matchbook-style catalog with price list, in envelope.
  - Ford: Creating Images for Forty-Six Years, Undated (Box 25)
  - Who is Gio? Giorgio Armani parfums, 1992; LB 187 (Box 18)
    Two catalogs, cover page, and price list in portfolio inserted into a slipcase
  - Giorgio Armani Collection, Fall-Winter 1992-1993; LB 8; Giorgio Armani (Box 17)
  - Giorgio Armani Collection, Fall-Winter 1992-1993; LB 8; Giorgio Armani (Box 17)
  - Gucci Collection, Spring-Summer 1999; LB 37; Gucci (Box 17)
  - Gucci Holiday, Winter 1999; LB 39; Gucci (Box 17)
  - Gucci Collection, Spring-Summer 2000; LB 42; Gucci (Box 17)
  - Gucci Collection, Fall-Winter 2001-2002; LB 67; Gucci (Box 17)
  - Gucci Jewelry, Undated; LB 179 (Box 18)
  - Harry Winston, Undated; LB 153 (Box 22)
  - Hermes Equipage, 1992; LB 164 (Box 18)
  - La Cravate Hermes, Fall-Winter 1998-1999; LB 174 (Box 18)
  - Hermes Ties, Fall-Winter 2000-2001; LB 46; Hermes (Box 17)
  - Hermes, Spring-Summer 2003; LB 83 (Box 17)
  - Hermes Le Monde D'Hermes, Fall-Winter 2003; LB 86; Hermes (Box 17)
  - Hermes Ties, Fall-Winter 2003; Hermes (Box 18)
  - Hermes Ties, Spring-Summer 2004; LB 127; Hermes (Box 18)
  - Hermes Ties, Spring-Summer 2005; LB 142; Hermes (Box 18)
    Business card attached: Andrew Kim
  - Hermes Ties, Fall-Winter 2005; LB 145; Hermes (Box 18)
    Business Card attached: Andrew Kim
  - Hermes Ties, Fall-Winter 2006; LB 144; Hermes (Box 18)
  - About Men Hermes, Autumn-Winter 2010; Hermes (Box 34)
  - Hermes Ties, Autumn-Winter 2016; Hermes (Box 34)
  - Hermes Ties, Spring-Summer 2018; Hermes (Box 34)
  - Holland & Holland, Spring-Summer 1997; LB 23 (Box 17)
  - Holland & Holland Sporting Guns, 1997; LB 26; Holland & Holland (Box 17)
  - James Locke & Co. LTD Milliner, Undated; LB 117; Sylvia Fletcher (Box 18)
  - Jil Sander Collection, Spring-Summer 1992; LB 2; Jil Sander (Box 24)
  - Jil Sander, Fall-Winter 1997-1998; LB 28 (Box 17)
  - Jil Sander, Winter 2000-2001; LB 177 (Box 18)
  - Jil Sander Collection, Spring-Summer 2004; LB 95 (Box 17)
    Runway
  - Kenzo Parfum d'ete (Summer), Undated; LB 158; Kanzo Takada (Box 19)
    Includes catalog with three loose color photographs in folder, closed with a twig
  - Le Carre Hermes Paris (Scarves), Fall-Winter 1992-1993; LB 3; Hermes (Box 17)
  - Le Sac Chanel, Undated; LB 172 (Box 18)
    Four cards held together by a gold band; band imprinted "RUNWAY SUCCESSES CHANEL". Includes accessories
  - L'Eau D'Issey, Undated; LB 189 (Box 24)
    Parfums, Issey Miyake, Paris
  - Leonard Collection, Fall-Winter 1992-1993; LB 10; Leonard (Box 17)
  - Longchamp Collection Fouladds, Spring 2000; LB 44; Longchamp (Box 17)
  - Loro Piana Cashmere Coarse-Hair, Fall 2004; LB 112 (Box 18)
    Swatchbook
  - Loro Piana, Fall-Winter 2004-2005; LB 147 (Box 18)
    Illustrations
  - Loro Piana Estrato Fotografico, Spring-Summer 2006; LB 137 (Box 18)
  - Louis Vuitton "icons", 2006; LB 141; Marc Jacobs (Box 18)
  - MaxMara Collection, Spring-Summer 2002; LB 73; MaxMara (Box 17)
  - MaxMara, Winter-Fall 2004; LB 125 (Box 18)
  - Missoni, Summer 2004; LB 110 (Box 17)
  - Missoni, Summer 2004; LB 130 (Box 24)
  - Opium/Yves Saint Laurent, 1991; LB 160 (Box 18)
    To be introduced February 1992. Look Book is undated; contains letter dated October 30, 1991. In a shiny black folder
  - Opium/Yves Saint Laurent, Undated; LB 156 (Box 18)
  - Prada Boutique, Spring-Summer 1993; LB 12; Prada (Box 17)
  - Prada, 1998; LB 166 (Box 18)
    Catalog and price list in mailing envelope
  - Prada Boutique, Accessories, 1998; LB 30; Prada (Box 17)
  - Prada Boutique, Accessories, 1998; LB 31; Prada (Box 17)
  - Prada Boutique, Accessories, 1998; LB 32; Prada (Box 17)
  - Prada, 1999; LB 167 (Box 18)
    Catalog and price list in mailing envelope, addressed to Dorothy Schefer. Includes sports and accessories
  - Prada, 1999; LB 168 (Box 18)
    Catalog and price list in mailing envelope, addressed to Dorothy Faux,. Includes sports and accessories
  - Prada, Spring 1999; LB 35 (Box 17)
  - Prada, 1999-2000; LB 163 (Box 18)
  - Prada Spring/Summer 2000, Spring-Summer 2000; LB 43; Prada (Box 17)
  - Prada Accessories, Spring-Summer 2001; LB 50; Prada (Box 17)
  - Prada Collection, Spring-Summer 2001; LB 58; Prada (Box 17)
  - Prada, Fall-Winter 2004; LB 126 (Box 18)
  - Prada, Fall-Winter 2004; LB 116 (Box 18)
  - Prada, Fall-Winter 2005; LB 128 (Box 18)
  - Prada, Fall-Winter 2005; LB 126 (Box 18)
  - Prada Milano Bags, 2005-2006; LB 111 (Box 19)
  - Prada, Spring-Summer 2007; LB 143 (Box 18)
  - Prada, Undated; LB 155 (Box 24)
  - Prada, Undated; LB 157 (Box 24)
  - Rafe NY Collection, Fall 2004; LB 101; Rafe (Box 18)
  - Ralph Lauren, Spring 1994; LB 15 (Box 18)
  - Ralph Lauren Collection, Fall 1994; LB 18; Ralph Lauren (Box 18)
    Includes letter and price list
  - Ralph Lauren Collection, Spring 1997; LB 25; Ralph Lauren (Box 18)
  - Ralph Lauren Black Label Collection, Spring 2001; LB 49; Ralph Lauren (Box 17)
  - Ralph Lauren Polo, Fall 2001; LB 63; Polo Ralph Lauren (Box 17)
  - Ralph Lauren Collection, Fall 2003; LB 151 (Box 18)
    Includes invitation and price list
  - Ralph Lauren Purple Label, Fall 2003; LB 87; Ralph Lauren (Box 17)
  - Ralph Lauren Black Label, Fall 2003; LB 129; Ralph Lauren (Box 17)
  - Ralph Lauren HOLIDAY, Winter 2003; LB 79; Ralph Lauren (Box 18)
  - Ralph Lauren Collection, Spring 2004; LB 107 (Box 17)
  - Ralph Lauren Collection, Fall 2004; LB 113 (Box 18)
    Trend Report inside
  - Ralph Lauren, Fall 2004; LB 123 (Box 18)
  - Ralph Lauren Home, Spring 2005; LB 103; Ralph Lauren (Box 18)
  - Ralph Lauren Black Label, Summer 2005; LB 90 (Box 18)
  - Ralph Lauren Collection, Fall 2005; Ralph Lauren (Box 18)
  - Ralph Lauren "The Ultimate Experience", Fall 2005; LB 121 (Box 18)
  - Ralph Lauren Black Label, Fall 2005; LB 131 (Box 18)
  - Ralph Lauren, Spring 2006; LB 133 (Box 18)
  - Ralph Lauren Blue Label Collection, Spring 2006; LB 134 (Box 18)
  - Ralph Lauren Home, Spring 2006; LB 136 (Box 18)
  - Ralph Lauren Collection, Spring 2007; LB 139 (Box 18)
  - Ralph Lauren Black Label, Spring 2007; LB 149 (Box 18)
    Includes price list.
  - Roger Vivier, Spring-Summer 2007; LB 146 (Box 18)
  - Ralph Lauren, Undated; LB 115 (Box 17)
  - Romeo Gigli, Fall-Winter 1992-1993; LB 11 (Box 17)
  - Romeo Gigli, Undated; LB 15 (Box 17)
  - Sheseido Parfum, 1993; LB 159 (Box 22)
    Includes oversized card (New Year's 1993) from Serge Lutens to Dorothy Schefer
  - Shiseido, Spring-Summer 1997; LB 24; Serge Lutens (Box 17)
  - Style.com The Best Looks of Spring 2001, Spring 2001; LB 140 (Box 18)
    Includes Calvin Klein, Lee Angel, Jean-Paul Gaultier, Marc Jacobs, Tuleh, Oliver Peoples, Miguel Androver, Christian Louboutin, Roberto Cavalli, Megan Park, Manolo Blahnik, Narciso Rodriguez, Oscar de la Renta, Sigerson Morrison, lambertson truex. Card in folder
  - Thierry Mugler Collection, Spring-Summer 1983; LB 1; Thierry Mugler (Box 24)
    Illustrations; individual sheets in portfolio
  - Tiffany & Co., 2005; LB 148 (Box 18)
  - Tiffany & Co. The Blue Book, 2006-2007; LB 150 (Box 18)
  - Tod's, Undated; LB 120 (Box 17)
  - TSE, Undated Spring; LB 99 (Box 17)
    Consists of separate cards in a slipcase
  - TSE, Spring-Summer 2001; LB 51 (Box 17)
    Individual cards in a jacket/envelope
  - TSE Five Easy Pieces, Fall-Winter 2002-2003; LB 77 (Box 17)
  - TSE, Fall 2003; LB 92 (Box 17)
  - TSE, Fall 2004; LB 124 (Box 18)
  - Untitled, Undated; LB 182 (Box 18)
    Spiral bound book of photographs, two to a page, numbered 1 through 70, mostly women's, some men's, no designer given but possibly Betsey Johnson.
  - Van Cleef & Arpels (Jewelry), Spring-Summer 2001; LB 59; Van Cleef & Arpels (Box 17)
  - Gianni Versace Collezione Donna Primavera Estate 1992, Spring-Summer 1992; LB 154; Versace, Gianni (Box 22)
    N.22
  - Versace LB 35, Fall-Winter 1998-1999; LB 33; Versace (Box 24)
    Individual leaves in a slipcase
  - Versace, Spring-Summer 1999 (Box 25)
  - Versace, Spring-Summer 2000; LB 171 (Box 18)
  - Versace Spring Summer Women's Collection, Spring-Summer 2000; LB 176 (Box 18)
  - Versace Fall Winter Women's Collection, Fall-Winter 2000-2001; LB 165 (Box 18)
  - Versace Collection, Spring-Summer 2001; LB 53; Versace (Box 17)
  - Versace Collection, Fall-Winter 2001-2002; LB 65; Versace (Box 17)
  - Versace Collection, Fall-Winter 2001-2002; LB 65; Versace (Box 17)
  - Versace Collection, Spring-Summer 2002; LB 72; Versace (Box 17)
  - Versace Accessories, Spring-Summer 2002; LB 71; Versace (Box 17)
  - Versace Collection, Fall-Winter 2002-2003; LB 75; Versace (Box 17)
  - Versace Holiday, Winter 2003; LB 98 (Box 17)
  - Versace Accessories, Spring-Summer 2004; LB 105 (Box 17)
  - Versace Accessories, Fall-Winter 2004-2005; LB 118 (Box 18)
  - Very Valentino, Fall-Winter 1992; LB 6; Valentino (Box 24)
  - Yves Saint Laurent (YSL Rive Guache), Fall-Winter 1992-1993; LB 5; Yves Saint Laurent (YSL) (Box 17)
  - Yves Saint Laurent (YSL Rive Guache), Spring-Summer 1994; LB 17; Yves Saint Laurent (YSL) (Box 17)
    Business card attached: Nicole Hartofiles
  - Yves Saint Laurent "Rive Gauche", Fall-Winter 2002-2003; LB 76; Yves Saint Laurent (YSL) (Box 17)
- Trend reports, 1975-1996
  - Vogue trend reports, 1987-1988
    - Volume 1, 1987-1988; TREND 1-39 (Box 20)
      Also contains the Fall/Winter 1988 accessories catalog
    - Volume 2, 1987-1988; TREND 40-71 (Box 20)
  - Other trend reports, 1975, 1991-1996
    Arranged chronologically.
    - Seventeen's Springcast, Spring 1975 (Box 22)
    - Seventeen's Fallcast, Fall 1975 (Box 22)
    - Jil Sander Annual Report, 1991; TREND 72 (Box 22)
      In with the Vogue Trend Reports
    - Twentysomething: The New Individual, 1992-05; The Roper Organization, Inc. (Box 26)
    - Allure Research Report: June 1992 to January 1993, 1993; Allure (Box 28)
    - Olfactive Trends for Women: An Awakening of the Senses, 1996; Firmenich (Box 26)
    - Men's Fragrance Trends, 1996-03-15; Christian Dior; Firmenich (Box 26)
    - Christian Dior: IFF Trend Presentation, 1996-03-15; Christian Dior (Box 26)
    - The Mademoiselle Report: Redefining a Generation, Undated; Roper Starch Worldwide; Mademoiselle (Box 26)
- Event publications, 1964-2001
  - Bonnie Cashin: designer's season descriptions and/or illustrations, 1964-1982; Cashin, Bonnie
    Now in binders, originally stapled packets, these written materials were handed out to buyers at the opening presentation of each season's new design line, by Bonnie Cashin. Includes one drawing and written descriptions by Bonnie Cashin and Philip Sills about the fashion designs for the upcoming season.
    - Bonnie Cashin for Sills, Spring Resort 1964, Spring-Summer 1964; EVENT 1 (Box 20)
    - Bonnie Cashin for Sills, Fall/Winter 1964-1965, Fall-Winter 1964-1965; EVENT 2 (Box 20)
    - Bonnie Cashin for Sills, Spring Resort 1965, Spring-Summer 1965; EVENT 3 (Box 20)
    - Bonnie Cashin for Sills, Fall/Winter 1965-1966, Fall-Winter 1965-1966; EVENT 4 (Box 20)
    - Bonnie Cashin for Sills, Spring 1966, Spring 1966; EVENT 5 (Box 20)
    - Bonnie Cashin for Sills, Spring 1966, Spring 1966; EVENT 6 (Box 20)
    - Bonnie Cashin for Sills, 20th Anniversary Fall/Winter 1966-1967, Fall-Winter 1966-1967; EVENT 7 (Box 20)
    - Bonnie Cashin for Sills, Fall/Winter 1967-1968, Fall-Winter 1967-1968; EVENT 8 (Box 20)
    - Bonnie Cashin for Sills, Spring 1969, Spring 1969; EVENT 9 (Box 20)
    - Bonnie Cashin for Sills, 'IF' Fall/Winter 1970-1971, Fall-Winter 1970-1971; EVENT 10 (Box 20)
    - Bonnie Cashin for Sills, Spring 1971, Spring 1971; EVENT 11 (Box 20)
    - Bonnie Cashin for Sills, Spring 1973, Spring 1973; EVENT 12 (Box 20)
    - Bonnie Cashin for Sills, Fall/Winter 1973-1974, Fall-Winter 1973-1974; EVENT 13 (Box 20)
    - Bonnie Cashin for Sills, Fall/Winter 1975-1976, Fall-Winter 1975-1976; EVENT 14 (Box 20)
    - Bonnie Cashin for Sills, Spring 1976, Spring 1976; EVENT 15 (Box 20)
    - Bonnie Cashin for Sills, Fall/Winter 1976-1977, Fall-Winter 1976-1977; EVENT 16 (Box 20)
    - Bonnie Cashin for Cashin Country, Fall/Winter 1979-1980, Fall-Winter 1979-1980; EVENT 17 (Box 20)
    - Bonnie Cashin Lecture, "Building a Career, Building a Life", 1982; EVENT 18 (Box 20)
  - Exhibit catalogs, 1989-2000
    - Una Donna, 1989; EXCAT 12; Roversi, Paolo; Gigli, Romeo; Carla Sozzani Editore srl (Box 19)
      Exhibit took place on September 12 -16, 1989. In slipcase.
    - Bare Witness-Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1996 (Box 22)
    - Dresses from the Collection of Diana, Princess of Wales-Christie's Auction, 1997-06-25; EXCAT 1 (Box 22)
    - Couture Collection of Tina Chow-Christie's, 1993-09; EXCAT 2 (Box 22)
    - Waves: Fifty Years of Textiles at Goldsmiths, 2000; EXCAT 3 (Box 22)
      In Memory of Constance Howard M.B.E.
    - David and Lynn Weinstein Collection-Christie's and the Lalique Society of America, 1993-08-16-1993-09-12; EXCAT 4 (Box 22)
    - Geoffrey Beene-Exhibition at the National Academy of Design, 1998-10-09; EXCAT 5 (Box 22)
    - Modern Accessories-Exhibit, Undated; EXCAT 6 (Box 22)
      Nine West
    - Origins Robert Lee Morris Artwear, 1992; EXCAT 7; Morris, Robert Lee (Box 22)
      Misagal, Theresa
    - Couture- Auction of Couturier, Antique Clothing and Accessories, 1993-09-30; EXCAT 8 (Box 22)
    - Vanities: Art of the Dressing Table, Fall 2013; Metropolitan Museum of Art Bulletin (Box 25)
    - Images from Sheer Realities: Clothing and Power in Nineteenth Century Philippines, February 2000; Roces, Marian Pastor; Oshima, Neal (Box 25)
      Inserts in paper case
    - Comme des Garcons:Art of the In-Between, September 2017; Kawakubo, Rei; Metropolitan Museum of Art (Box 34)
  - Various event publications, 1976, 1997-2001
    - ASME Luncheon, 1976 (Box 22)
      Summary by the editor of Glamour
      Wilson, Phyllis Starr; Mirabella, Grace
    - New York Collections, Fall 1997; EVENT 19 (Box 22)
    - Sotheby's Auction-Nothing to Wear, Spring 1998; EVENT 21 (Box 22)
    - Legends and Leaders -Achiever Award Dinner, May 24, 2000; EVENT 26 (Box 24)
    - Christie's Auction of Personal property of Marilyn Monroe, October 27-28, 1999; EVENT 28 (Box 22)
    - NYC Fashion Shows-Fashion Week, Fall 2000 (Box 22)
      Sponsored by General Motors and managed by 7th on Sixth
    - American Fashion Awards, June 15, 2000 (Box 22)
      Presented by the Council of Fashion Designers of America
    - American Fashion Awards, June 14, 2001 (Box 22)
    - NY Times Men's Shows, Spring 1998; EVENT 29 (Box 24)
    - On Pride and Prejudice in the Arts, 1997; Gombrich, Ernst; Pentagram Papers (Box 25)
      Pentagram Papers 26
    - Of Money and the Divine, 2000; Crawford, Tad; Pentagram Papers (Box 34)
      Pentagram Papers 28
    - New York Premiere of Mikhail Baryshnikov's Production of Cinderella, April 24, 1984; Ballet Theatre Foundation, Inc.; Metropolitan Opera House (Box 25)
    - The International Best Dressed Poll, 2015; Vanity Fair (Box 25)
    - The International Best Dressed Poll, 2013; Vanity Fair (Box 25)
    - The International Best Dressed Poll, 2017; Vanity Fair (Box 34)
    - Program for the Twenty-Fourth Annual Million Dollar Beauty Ball to Benefit the Greater New York March of Dimes, April 12, 1999; March of Dimes (Box 26)
    - VH1 Fashion and Music Awards, December 3, 1995; VH1 (Box 27)
    - Achiever Award Black and White Dinner, May 24, 2000; Estée Lauder Companies, Inc. (Box 27)
    - Council of Fashion Designers of America Awards, 1991-1997; CFDA (Box 28)
- Fashion publications
  - Books, 1987-2006
    - The Dale Sko Hack: Exploring Modes of Production and Re-Form Tactics and The Dale Sko Hack, Design Management: A Reinterpretation, a lecture at Istanbul Technical University, 2006; BOOK 2; von Busch, Otto (Box 17)